wavebroadband.com 2017-03-09

# 1-866-WAVE-123 | wavebroadband.com

ECPA or the Register/Trace Statute, the Cable Act’s requirements are different depending on          Access to Our Records About You.
the nature of the information sought. If the governmental authority wants disclosure of re-          Under the Cable Act, cable subscribers have the right to inspect our records that contain person-
cords revealing cable subscriber selection of video programming, then we may disclose it only        ally identifiable information about them and to have a reasonable opportunity to correct any
if authorized or required by a court order and only if the two special requirements of the Cable     errors in such information. If you wish to exercise this right, please notify us at the local Wave
Act stated above are met. If, however, the government seeks any other kind of personally             Broadband office specified on your bill, and we will contact you to arrange a mutually conve-
identifiable information, then those two special requirements do not have to be met and the          nient time during our regular business hours.
government may require us to make the disclosure if authorized by the ECPA or the Register/
Trace Statute. In some cases, this will mean that the disclosure may be required without a court     Your Rights Under the Cable Act.
order, without any prior notice to you that the government seeks the disclosure, without any         The Cable Act provides you with a cause of action for damages, attorneys’ fees and costs in
prior opportunity for you to oppose the disclosure and without any notice that the disclosure        Federal District Court if we violate the Cable Act’s limitations on the collection, disclosure, and
has been made as required.                                                                           retention of personally identifiable information about you.
In addition to the above, if you subscribe to any of our Internet or telephony services, the ECPA    Contact Your Local Wave Broadband Office If You Have Questions.
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          PRIVACY POLICY
permits us to disclose the contents of your e-mail or other communications to a law enforce-         If you have any questions about our policies described in this Notice, please contact your local
ment agency if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death           Wave Broadband office at the address and telephone listed on your bill (or, if you have not yet        At Wave Broadband we take your privacy seriously and we want you to know our
or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of the information without delay.       been billed, on the service order you signed to subscribe to the service).                             policies. This Notice will give you an overview of those policies and how we will apply
We may do so without prior notice to you, without your consent and without being required                                                                                                                   them in specific situations.
to do so by a warrant, subpoena, court order or law. Examples of situations in which we might
make such disclosures are where we reasonably believe that there is an immediate risk of death,                                                                                                             The Cable Communications Policy Act of 1984 (the “Cable Act”) contains restrictions
suicide or terrorist activity.                                                                                                                                                                              on the collection, disclosure and retention by cable operators of personally identifi-
                                                                                                                                                                                                            able information about subscribers to cable television or certain other services. Other
The ECPA provides for other exceptional circumstances under which we may be compelled                                                                                                                       federal law also may apply to some services, including the Electronic Communications
or permitted to disclose personally identifiable information about you or the content of your                                                                                                               Privacy Act of 1986 (the “ECPA”). This Notice informs subscribers of our policies re-
communications. For example, the content of your e-mail or other communications may be                                                                                                                      garding personally identifiable information we obtain in the course of providing our
disclosed to law enforcement agencies if it appears to be evidence of child pornography, or was                                                                                                             services that are subject to the privacy provisions of the Cable Act. Those services cur-
inadvertently obtained by us and appears to pertain to the commission of a crime.                                                                                                                           rently consist of our video programming service, our Internet access service, our tele-
                                                                                                                                                                                                            phone service (including our voice over Internet Protocol telephone service). Not all of
The Social Security Act provides that state welfare agencies may obtain from our subscriber lists                                                                                                           these services may be available in your local cable system. Our policies are intended to
the names and addresses of individuals who owe or are owed child support and the names and                                                                                                                  conform to the requirements of the Cable Act, the ECPA and other applicable law. The
addresses of their employers. The law says that this information can be obtained through an                                                                                                                 term “Wave Broadband,” “we,” “our” or “us” refers to any company that is controlled by
administrative subpoena issued by the state welfare agency, without a court order, and does                                                                                                                 WaveDivision Holdings, LLC, a Delaware limited liability company, and through which
not require that a subscriber be given notice of and the opportunity to contest the disclosure.                                                                                                             you subscribe to any cable or other service covered by the privacy provisions of the
                                                                                                                                                                                                            Cable Act or other laws mentioned in this Notice.
Sometimes, a copyright owner believes that the copyright has been infringed by an Internet user
who uses an online service to post, download or otherwise use the copyrighted work without                                                                                                                  Policy Overview. This Notice tells you our policies regarding:
permission. The owner may know some information, such as the user’s e-mail or IP address,
but may not know the users true identity. The Digital Millennium Copyright Act provides for a                                                                                                               • The kinds of personally identifiable information we collect;
copyright owner to obtain a subpoena seeking disclosure from an online service provider of the                                                                                                              • How we use that information;
identity of a user who is believed to have infringed the copyright. Upon receipt of a subpoena,                                                                                                             • The nature, frequency and purpose of any disclosure we may make of
the online service provider is required to expeditiously identify the alleged infringer.                                                                                                                      that information and the types of persons and entities to which the
                                                                                                                                                                                                              disclosure may be made;
Wave Broadband will disclose personally identifiable information about you when required by                                                                                                                 • The period during which we will keep that information;
law or legal process, after giving effect to the Cable Act’s requirements.                                                                                                                                  • The choices available to you regarding collection, use and disclosure
                                                                                                                                                                                                              of that information, including the times and place at which you may
Time Period During Which We Retain Personally Identifiable Information.                                                                                                                                       have access to that information; and
The Cable Act requires us to destroy personally identifiable information if the information is no                                                                                                           • Certain rights you may have regarding that information.
longer necessary for the purpose for which it was collected and there are no pending requests
by you for access to it or pending court orders or other legal process requiring that we disclose it                                                                                                        Information is “personally identifiable” if it can be used to identify or contact an in-
to a third party. In most cases, this means that we will have personally identifiable information                                                                                                           dividual, such as his or her name and address or telephone number. It also includes
about you for so long as you are a subscriber and continue to retain it thereafter for as long as                                                                                                           information that links data about an individual’s activities or history to that individual,
it may reasonably be required to comply with tax, accounting and any applicable contractual                                                                                                                 such as the combination of the individual’s name with the fact that he or she pur-
or legal requirements, which could be seven years or more after you stop being a subscriber.                        1-866-WAVE-123 | wavebroadband.com
                                                                                                  5                                                                                                       6                                                                                             1
                                                                                                                                                                                               WBB.011.1014

chased a specific product online, so that someone else with access to the combined information        policies that govern your use of our services; and                                                   • Persons or entities that control, are controlled by, or under common control with Wave Broad-
could learn that the named person bought the particular item. Information that does not per-          • Other information that we need to render a service to you or conducting our business of            band;
mit an individual to be identified or contacted and that does not permit information about his        providing that service.                                                                              • Billing services, collection agencies and credit agencies;
or her activities or history to be linked to him or her is not “personally identifiable information.”                                                                                                      • Installation, repair and other contractors and subcontractors or suppliers of goods or services
Among other things, this means that if we separate data about your activities from your name          In general, we use this personally identifiable information as necessary to render our services      we use in providing a service to you;
or other data that identifies you, then that data is no longer “personally identifiable informa-      to you, to detect unauthorized reception of cable communications and for tax, legal, accounting      • Sales representatives used to market our services;
tion.” For example, we might compile data we have about our Wave Broadband Internet access            and other purposes related to our business of providing our services to subscribers, including,      • Accountants, lawyers, consultants and other professionals we or our affiliated companies use
customers into aggregate or other anonymous forms, such as the monthly average number of              but not limited to, the following:                                                                   in our businesses; and
customers who use the service to visit travel-related Websites.                                                                                                                                            • Cable programming or content suppliers and program guide distributors.
                                                                                                      • To make sure you are being billed properly and pay for the services you receive;
Our policies described in this Notice apply to personally identifiable information about you that     • To send you pertinent announcements about the Wave Broadband services you receive;                 In addition, if Wave Broadband or its affiliates directly or indirectly transfer ownership of or an
you furnish to us or that we otherwise collect in the course of providing you with one of our ser-    • To improve the quality of Wave Broadband’s services;                                               interest in all or part of the business of providing a service you subscribe for, we may disclose
vices. Those policies apply to such information whether we obtain it “online” (such as when you       • To answer questions from subscribers such as troubleshooting; and                                  or transfer your subscriber records to the purchaser or other party to the extent necessary to
subscribe for our cable service on a Website we operate) or “offline” (such as when you subscribe     • To send promotional material or information to you about other products and services avail-        complete the transaction or permit the purchaser or other party to continue to provide you
for our cable service using the telephone or a paper order form). Please note, however, that if       able from Wave Broadband or others, subject to applicable law and any “opt-out” choice you           with service after the transaction is completed. This kind of transaction could take the form of a
you use a Website we operate for purposes of our cable or other services, then additional online      make as described in this Notice.                                                                    merger, sale of stock or assets, formation of a joint venture, investment or some other structure.
privacy policies may apply that cover topics unique to Internet usage, such as use of “cookies.”
You can review those additional online policies by clicking on the “Privacy Policy” link appearing                                                                                                         Information we disclose for purposes relating to billing and levels of service usage is generally
                                                                                                      Without your written or electronic consent, we may not collect this personally identifiable in-
at the bottom of the home page of the relevant Website.                                                                                                                                                    provided on a monthly basis. Information for other purposes is provided as it is needed.
                                                                                                      formation about you over our cable system unless it is necessary to render a service you receive
                                                                                                      or detect unauthorized reception of cable communications. If you use the Wave Broadband
Some of our services, including our Internet access service, interactive cable television pro-                                                                                                             As permitted by the Cable Act, we may also from time to time disclose lists of our subscribers to
                                                                                                      Internet access service, an interactive television service or a telephone service (including voice
gramming and telephone service (including voice over Internet Protocol telephone service) al-                                                                                                              third parties for purposes other than those referred to above. Those lists may contain your name
                                                                                                      over Internet Protocol telephone service)we provide, then as a necessary incident of provid-
low you to interact with companies and individuals that are independent of Wave Broadband.                                                                                                                 and address, so long as we have given you the opportunity to prohibit or limit such disclosure
                                                                                                      ing that service, our computer systems automatically capture and store information that may
By using those services, you may enable these companies or individuals to independently learn                                                                                                              and we do not also reveal, directly or indirectly, the extent of any viewing or other use of the
                                                                                                      include, but is not limited to, the interactive television service offerings you order using such
personally identifiable information about you. The policies in this Notice do not apply to per-                                                                                                            services we provide to you or the nature of any transaction you make using those services. This
                                                                                                      interactive television service and the Websites you visit using such Internet access service; the
sonally identifiable information or other information that you provide to any of these third                                                                                                               permits us, among other things, to disclose your name and address to charities, advertisers,
                                                                                                      dates, times and length of your Internet visits or telephone calls; the IP (Internet Protocol) ad-
parties or that they collect independently of us. These third parties may not be obligated to                                                                                                              direct mail marketers and telemarketers for use in telephone or mail solicitations, market re-
                                                                                                      dress of the computer you use or e-mail addresses or telephone numbers that you communicate
comply with Wave Broadband’s privacy policies or the privacy provisions of the Cable Act. They                                                                                                             search or other purposes. You have the right to elect not to be included on such a list. If you do
                                                                                                      with; and the text of e-mail or other electronic communications you send or receive using any of
may have their own privacy policies, but Wave Broadband is not responsible or liable to you if                                                                                                             not desire to be included on any such list, you may “opt out” by contacting your local
                                                                                                      these services. We use that information to provide the service, to bill and collect service-related
such third parties do not have appropriate policies or if they fail to follow those policies.                                                                                                              Wave Broadband cable office (which is identified on each monthly bill you receive),
                                                                                                      charges, to ensure compliance with applicable law and contractual provisions and to customize
                                                                                                                                                                                                           or by writing to us at Wave Broadband at 401 Parkplace Center, Suite 500, Kirkland
                                                                                                      our services based on the interests of subscribers and for tax, legal, accounting and other pur-
The Kinds of Personally Identifiable Information We Collect and How We Use It.                                                                                                                             WA 98033. If you use the Wave Broadband Internet access service or telephone service (includ-
                                                                                                      poses related to our business of providing such services. Any personally identifiable informa-
In order to provide our services to you, we keep business records that contain personally identi-                                                                                                          ing voice over Internet Protocol telephone service) to send or receive an email message or other
                                                                                                      tion that may be derived from these logs is subject to the policies described in this Notice and to
fiable information about you, including but not limited to the following:                                                                                                                                  electronic communication, the ECPA permits us to access the content of those communications.
                                                                                                      our obligations under the ECPA and other applicable law.
                                                                                                                                                                                                           It also permits us to disclose such information to an addressee or intended recipient (or his or
• Your name, home and work e-mail and postal addresses, telephone numbers, social security                                                                                                                 her agent); to a person involved in forwarding such information to its destination or when it is
                                                                                                      We may also combine personally identifiable information that we obtain from you in the course
number, driver’s license number, credit or debit card numbers and expiration dates and bank                                                                                                                necessarily incident to providing service or to protect our rights or property; or to any one with
                                                                                                      of our business of providing a service to you with personally identifiable information that we
account information for billing purposes, payment history and credit reports;                                                                                                                              the consent of the subscriber or an addressee or intended recipient (or his or her agent). The
                                                                                                      obtain from third parties for the purpose of creating an enhanced personal database to use in
• Depending on the services we provide to you, information on the number, location within                                                                                                                  Cable Act also permits us to disclose personally identifiable information about you if authorized
                                                                                                      marketing and other activities.
your home and configuration of television sets, converters, cable modems, personal computers,                                                                                                              by a court order and if you have been notified of such order. If a governmental authority seeks
telephones or other service-related equipment or devices in your home;                                                                                                                                     the disclosure of personally identifiable information under any law except (i) the ECPA or (ii) the
                                                                                                      Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information by Us.
• Maintenance and repair records for the equipment in your home used for the services;                                                                                                                     federal “pen register/trap and trace” statute (which we refer to as the “Register/Trace Statute”),
                                                                                                      Under the Cable Act, Wave Broadband may not disclose personally identifiable information
• The services and service options you select and, in the case of any service where you have                                                                                                               then the Cable Act may prohibit such disclosure unless the disclosure is required by a court order
                                                                                                      about you except in certain limited circumstances.
a choice of whether or not to use a particular feature, program or offering, the information                                                                                                               and the following two special requirements are met:
transmitted through our cable facilities or that you otherwise communicate to us in order to
                                                                                                      We may disclose personally identifiable information about you with your prior written or elec-
make a choice;                                                                                                                                                                                             • you have been given the opportunity to appear and contest in court any claims made in sup-
                                                                                                      tronic consent. As permitted by the Cable Act, Wave Broadband also may disclose from time to
• Information about your satisfaction or usage of a service that we obtain from subscriber                                                                                                                 port of the court order sought by the governmental authority; and
                                                                                                      time, without such consent, personally identifiable information about you if necessary to ren-
interviews or questionnaires or other feedback from you;                                                                                                                                                   • in the court proceeding, the governmental authority has offered clear and convincing evi-
                                                                                                      der, or conduct a legitimate business activity related to, a cable service or other service provided
• A record of whether you rent or own your home so that we can obtain any permission re-                                                                                                                   dence that you are reasonably suspected of engaging in criminal activity and that the informa-
                                                                                                      to you. The kinds of persons or entities to which we may make such disclosures (to the extent
quired prior to installing our cable or equipment;                                                                                                                                                         tion sought would be material evidence in a case against you.
                                                                                                      permitted by the Cable Act) include, but are not necessarily limited to, the following:
• Subscriber correspondence (via e-mail or otherwise);
• A record of any violations and alleged violations of the agreements, terms, conditions or                                                                                                                If a governmental authority seeks personally identifiable information about you under the
                                                                                                   2                                                                                                     3                                                                                                   4
